Maryland Citizens Against State Executions Records
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Subject Files, 1998-2013; Undated; nam_apap340-3; 1.4 cubic ft.
  - Press/Articles, 2006-2007; nam_apap340-3_52 (Box 1, Folder 49-50)
  - Baze v Recs/Lethal Injection articles, 2007; nam_apap340-3_53 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Governor O'Malley, 2007; nam_apap340-3_54 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - MD CASE General, 2007; nam_apap340-3_55 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Misc Articles, 2007; nam_apap340-3_56 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - MRJ 990, 2007; nam_apap340-3_57 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Newspaper Ads, 2007; nam_apap340-3_58 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Newspaper Archives, 2007; nam_apap340-3_59 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Venable, 2007; nam_apap340-3_60 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Articles, 2007-2008; nam_apap340-3_61 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Lethal Injection/Baze articles, 2007-2008; nam_apap340-3_62 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - MD CASE 990 FY, 2007-2008; nam_apap340-3_63 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Session Articles, 2007-2008; nam_apap340-3_64 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Press, 2007-2009; nam_apap340-3_65 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Press, 2007-2008; 2011; nam_apap340-3_66 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - ACLU Spy Report & Articles, 2008; nam_apap340-3_67 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Commission Press, 2008; nam_apap340-3_68 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - JFI Contract, 2008; nam_apap340-3_69 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - MD CASE Board Meeting Minutes and Materials, 2008; nam_apap340-3_70 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - MD Spying, 2008; nam_apap340-3_71 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Kevin Jones Case, 2008-2009; nam_apap340-3_72 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 2008-2009; nam_apap340-3_73 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Newspaper: Gazette, 2009 February 27; nam_apap340-3_74 (Flat-file 3)
  - Loan Agreement EJUSA, 2009; nam_apap340-3_75 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Baltimore County, Undated; nam_apap340-3_76 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - For Rion - Notes, Undated; nam_apap340-3_77 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Frosh, Brian = Chair & Senate 3rd Proceedings Committee, Undated; nam_apap340-3_78 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - MD CASE Documents, Undated; nam_apap340-3_79 (Cd 7)
  - Unlabeled Printed Digital Photograph, Undated; nam_apap340-3_80 (Box 2, Folder 13)